MY BELOVED DEMON
A hidden camera?
Haida
What the…
Well…
I was just covering our faces
so that he does not recognize us.
Rightly so.
Why did your powers suddenly stop working?
And really? Why didn't they work?
But To Kyung.
He left.
Where did he go?
Did he go outside?
STORAGE CAMERA
We won't let No To Kyung see this.
What was he looking for here?
Has he already taken it?
What are you looking for?
You are the woman who talked about Arabic.
Arabic?
Coffee?
What are you looking for?
I know this place very well, so tell me.
Who are you?
And who do I look like?
- To beggar.
- Bingo.
I accept money orders.
JESUS CORPORATION
BANK "TEKUK"
"The Jesus Corporation"?
Sounds pretty reliable, right?
Where did you sneak in?
I didn't sneak up on you.
You just didn't notice me.
And it wasn't me who climbed in here.
You came to my territory.
Your area?
I have the best seat here.
Warm and sunny.
We don't have time for that.
Blinking
That which flashes
will fade sooner rather than later.
Do you know her?
She is just another crazy person
with a corrupted soul.
Ignore her.
EPISODE 7
TENSE RELATIONSHIPS
Where did he go?
Let's pursue him.
This should be enough.
where are you going
I want to try something.
Everything is fine with my powers.
So what went wrong before?
First, let's find No To Kyung.
Shall we follow him inside?
No, it's too…
It's too risky.
That's enough for today.
That's Köne.
- What?
- Can we talk a little?
Are you seeing your psychiatrist now?
I want to take a break from treatment.
I am very busy right now.
oh one more thing
your father asked
what have you been doing lately
AND?
I told him that I don't know.
As expected.
So don't know anything.
That's Köne.
I can take care of myself.
That's why it's time to make appointments for me.
Psychiatrists cannot be trusted.
Mrs.
We had a great meditation today.
I have to attend a charity event tomorrow.
so can we change the meeting time?
Of course.
Thank you.
Bad connection?
What was the problem?
This makes the head spin.
Here it is.
The same thing happened that day.
The day I lost my strength.
I was almost hit by a car,
because the forces did not obey me.
And this is how my dad moved to you.
The problem is definitely in you.
If someone has a problem,
it's in you don't blame me
I don't blame you.
But my strength is like never before
didn't blink until we met.
And my dad didn't go to anyone.
Can't you hear yourself?
you accuse me of
that you were almost hit by a car
and that the tattoo passed to me.
And you blame me
in the flickering of your amazing powers.
I want to say that it will be bad
if they don't work again when they should.
- As before.
- "Bad"?
If it's so bad, why did you do it?
Do you think I liked it?
- Do you think I liked it?
- Did you like it?
Why is Mr. Pak not here yet?
I can't even
drink your coffee in peace.
where's the coffee
COMPLETION OF CONSTRUCTION
"SUNVOL THEATER"
"Sunwol Theater"...
Are you going to some newlyweds for a housewarming party?
They are not actually married.
and this is not a housewarming party.
I was just kidding. Don't be so harsh.
I'm not strict. But you are too relaxed.
There are many here. It seems that there is no need for this.
Have you ever heard this phrase?
"When a person comes,
then her whole life comes with her."
Here, life!
Here!
Is all this still like that?
My clothes, necessary things
and a small collection dear to me,
which reflects my taste.
- You call it a small collection?
- Yes.
It's like he moved in with me
the entire Sunvol Foundation.
That's because we
and "Sunvol Foundation" are inseparable.
Where should I put it?
These are my treasures. Put it here.
No, there is no room here.
- Put them in To To Hee's room, which is over there.
- Good.
No!
can we talk
And what is that? Can it wait?
You are not the only one who lives here.
We live in an apartment together.
And what?
Get rid of unnecessary things.
Then everything remains. I need everything.
- Get rid of it immediately.
- No.
Do you want to live in such a cluttered apartment?
What are you living for?
in such a tiny apartment?
It's not that the apartment is tiny.
Just yours
too many things, drive.
It's not just some stuff.
They all reflect my taste and history
and reveal who I am.
They are Jung Ku Won.
You leave me no choice.
Enjoy life
with my infinite other selves.
At least give me my coffee.
Thank you.
It finally comes out that you are married.
So what kind of marriage is that?
I can not even calmly bring
to this house your things?
How should I know? I'm sweet solo.
Not that you'd have a chance
but you shouldn't get married.
- Don't worry!
- My coffee!
Think what you say.
I will take things with me.
Go back inside.
No.
I have pride.
I can't come back like this.
You know how hard it was to get it.
do you know
Is everything so bad?
I will not drink it.
Maybe because of the garlic I ate.
Just such a marriage.
You talk as if you are married.
I got married.
- What?
- To be more precise, I was married.
When did it happen?
On a long vacation five years ago.
Just in case, I didn't tell anyone.
She did everything quietly.
This is the only
that I did well in that marriage.
Marriage is crazy in many ways.
Is this too?
I'm lucky.
Do you see? Everything went in.
How can she live in an apartment
smaller than a car?
The apartment is not too small.
And your greed is too great.
Look at all these things of yours.
She's so crazy
Who is this?
"Who is this?"
Mr. Who, won't you come back?
You told me to live with my other selves.
Did he just run away from home?
Did he run away after one day?
I have to teach him.
I will never call him.
It was not necessary...
When did he hide it here?
Unbelievable. You kicked me out.
It's time for you to go.
Go work on your performance.
The point is that Star Chin is gone,
when I found out about your wedding.
Press conference tomorrow
and she is not in touch.
And she misses rehearsals.
Can you go talk to her?
Why should I?
She probably thinks
that her guardian is betraying her.
leave it Cancel the show if it doesn't come back.
- I can't just...
- Go.
- Anyway...
- Just go!
What is it anyway?
He has too many of these selves.
The ego has already multiplied.
You bought yourself a rag.
A rag?
The one who is always there.
You take this person for granted
so you neglect her
you blame everything
because you are so easy with her.
It was like that between us.
Is that why you threw me a surprise party?
What did I appreciate you?
you really wanted
for me to love you, right?
i like
that we treated each other that way.
This is how a real family should be.
Although we are not relatives,
we were family to each other.
I agree.
But don't worry.
No one can ever replace you.
SOK HOON
Hi Seok Hoon.
Hello To Hee. Where are you?
I want to talk to you alone.
About what?
This is about Mr. Jung Ku Won.
So you won't call me?
Then I'll just live in a car.
It's a little thing.
A little
Why so many things?
It's better here than in the apartment.
More spacious and comfortable.
I didn't know you were here, Ms. Sin.
I'm here because Mr. Chong
moved here today.
Of course.
- Shall we talk in the office?
- Of course.
What is the matter?
Has Mr. Jeon officially moved?
We must prevent rumors about our marriage.
What is it? Just say it already.
Is Jung Koo Won in trouble or something?
To Hee, how much do you know about him?
Well…
There is nothing to know about him.
Did you thoroughly investigate him before marriage?
Are you talking about his family or education?
I want to show you something.
This is from the completion ceremony
of the "Sunvol" theater back in 1977.
Look at this.
This is Mr. Chong.
He looks like a grandfather like two drops of water.
This is the past executive director.
Do you really think so?
And what else?
What are the dominant genes.
How are they so similar?
THE MAN CHOSEN BY TO TO HI
BEAUTY AND WEALTH CHEON KU WONA
No signal underground?
That's better.
Works
It works!
Oh, leave it.
I didn't know we were expecting a guest.
I had to talk to To Hee.
What exactly?
Let's go have a drink.
Aren't you curious about what To Hee and I were talking about?
Get down to business.
I don't want to take too long
leave To To Hee alone.
Don't worry.
Ms. Sin is with her.
That's good. I can trust her.
It seems that there are many things
which you and To Hee don't tell me.
That's because we have a very special relationship.
You're not human, are you?
What are you…
What do you mean?
I'm obviously human, right?
are you a vampire
Don't compare me
with those damn mosquitoes.
I find you very suspicious, Mr. Chong.
Isn't it because you just hate me?
This is also true.
When the speech has already come,
I plan to follow you.
If it becomes clear,
that you can hurt To Hee
I will not sit idly by, Mr. Chong.
What then?
I will dig up your secret
and I will tell it to the whole world.
I'm not afraid at all.
You don't know how to threaten at all.
I agree, I'm not a terrible person.
But I can definitely cause trouble.
I am very pushy.
I will constantly bother you and catch you up,
and you will no longer be able to live
in peace and quiet
which you enjoy every day.
you understand
one termite can
slowly chew through the wood like
that eventually the whole house will fall.
God, I have a new fan.
I'm too popular for my own good.
But you should not do this.
I am a concrete building.
Be there.
Come sit at the bar. He is around the corner.
Are you sure you don't want to?
Damage.
Want to sit at the bar?
I will give you free drinks and food
and meet hot men.
get up
- Come back if you change your mind!
- Why am I a boring boy?
What...
It hurts.
Go get me another drink!
I ordered to bring me another drink!
where are you hiding
Chin Ka Yeon!
Get out immediately!
Shall I spank you?
A good girl must obey
when father says to bring a drink
or fall down and die.
How dare you be rude to me?
The wretch
Got caught, you devilish rat.
Do you think you can hide from me?
who are you
What the hell are you doing in my house?
Congratulations.
I came to collect your debt.
Are you a loan shark?
OK, I'll give the money.
How many?
Ten years ago you sold my soul
for 100 million won.
And I came for her.
What? Ten years ago?
don't you remember
You were quite drunk even then.
Let me remind you.
You lost all your money at once
which I gave you
I thought it was a dream.
No.
Here is the proof.
Devil.
Take my soul if you can.
If you touch it with your finger,
I will cut off your whole arm!
This hand?
No need to gamble
how come you don't have talent and talent.
come out
No one will hurt you anymore.
are you an angel
I? Why do you think so?
You saved me.
Angels…
never come to the rescue.
Then who are you?
I am a demon.
You people call me the devil.
Daemon?
Sir!
Take me with you!
I do not sign agreements with children.
Then let's make deals!
I cook and wash well!
I can do everything well!
No, thank you.
I will find you.
I will find you in spite of everything,
and I...
Do you even know how hard it was to find you?
Can you imagine what I still have?
sorry is everything ok
Did your boyfriend leave you?
Stop crying, join us.
- Go away.
- Don't do it like that.
You can mess with me.
What the hell?
Go away, you scoundrel.
What? Say it again, scumbag.
is everything ok
- Let go.
- Oh, okay.
- Well, hit me.
- Small...
- Let go!
- Hit me, scoundrel!
Director Chon.
- Good.
- Let go.
- I understand, so let me go!
- Let's just go.
I knew you were back
you will come to save me
Almost there, Zirko Chin.
You are such a good girl.
Let's sit down.
That's it.
Director Chong,
you're not actually married, are you?
It's just for show, right?
Yes.
Okay then.
That's all I need to know.
God, I feel so sorry for her.
I've got a problem, Mr. Puck.
Not her.
And who?
Choo Seok Hoon will watch over me.
I told you
that you will break many hearts
if you marry To To Hee.
Conceived resentment is a terrible thing.
We have a big problem here.
And if he does something?
What exactly? I doubt it.
This does not bode well.
Signing papers again?
"Sunvol Foundation" does not stop its work
only because you are not here.
How is your marriage?
I don't know.
No way and inconvenient.
As expected.
Be that as it may, but it's easier for me
for To To Hee is eternally in my presence.
I'm talking about dad.
I feel relieved
because dad is always in my presence.
Seriously…
By the way, something strange happened today.
What exactly?
My strength
blinked
This is funny. What are they, a fluorescent lamp?
They suddenly stopped working.
But when I tried again,
everything was fine.
Maybe there was a bad connection.
I thought so
but it has happened to me before.
When I had an accident with To To Hee.
This is true.
you said about it
when they first lost their strength.
What were the symptoms before
how did they blink
I had the same dream this morning.
is it possible
what do you become human
Do I become a person?
The longer you stay without strength,
you remember more.
And the more you become a person,
then your strength becomes weaker.
You are right.
If you think about it,
it doesn't look like me to worry
sudden outbursts of the illogical
and unnecessary emotions.
Illogical and unnecessary emotions?
Some guilt and sympathy.
And who...
What?
That's all.
It really doesn't look like you.
Don't come forward until you get the tattoo back.
And if something happens when your powers…
Okay, I got it!
Don't bother me.
I'm not boring. I express concern.
when i get dad back
all…
will be back to normal, right?
And my strength...
and emotions.
"SUNVOL FOUNDATION"
How crazy.
So you came home at night?
You are not asleep yet.
How could I go to sleep
if you didn't even know where you were?
Were you worried about me?
If so.
people worry
even when the dog doesn't come home
but you don't understand.
- Since you are back, I will go to sleep.
- Hold on.
I want to recharge.
Recharge?
do you really think
that thanks to this
will your powers not flicker?
We have to try everything we can.
Maybe you need to make a new deal?
There are no signs of spontaneous combustion.
I must have exhausted my strength
when he moved us.
Then we have to be careful.
Ignore me and go to sleep.
I can't sleep when someone is around
so sleep alone.
Demons don't need to sleep.
Well, I think you won't sleep all night.
This illogical and unnecessary emotion,
which will soon disappear...
Mrs. Sin
Hello Ms. Sin?
We have a problem, Ms. To.
Who gained the most from the death of Chief Chu?
To To Hee.
Why should she not leave anything to the children,
successful CEOs,
and give everything to some girl?
This is illogical.
- More important...
Her will was changed…
On the day of Chairman Chu's death.
- On the day of Chairman Chu's death.
- ...the death of Chu head.
On the day of Chairman Chu's death.
- It is unclean with a will.
- She was cremated to destroy the evidence.
She…
What is she, the witch of the century?
PRINCESS "MIRE GROUP"
KILLED FOR INHERITANCE?
Did she kill for her inheritance?
What? What happened?
Madness.
DEATH OF THE HEAD OF THE MIRE GROUP CHU
DID THE CEO WANTED A HERITAGE?
No leniency.
Answer firmly!
- Yes, sir!
- Hello.
- Yes.
- We have to go to court.
- And you! you are done
- if you do not remove the article.
- Answer firmly!
"News-clickbait"
first released this fake,
which then went viral on social networks
and online communities.
Even the press got involved
to the spread of disinformation.
We went to court and removed the articles,
but we can't handle it
with all new articles.
What exactly did Mr. Lee hear at the wedding?
When will you release the story?
Today is a happy day.
Let him enjoy.
Mr. Lee thought
that it is a surprise gift.
It caught me by surprise.
The board of directors evaluates the candidates
for the position of chairman?
Yes.
But they will come together
to the detriment of the corporate image
and they will reject your candidacy.
Has the legal department gathered for a meeting?
- Yes.
- Please start without me.
Yes, ma'am.
Let me go talk
with council members.
I will try to convince those
who is on good terms with Aunt Jeong Suk…
Maybe we'll take the easy way first?
What exactly?
Why not us personally?
not convince the source of the rumor?
It is not so simple.
Those who professionally spread fakes,
are not afraid of almost anything.
Please give us time.
Let's try to do something.
Shall we visit that guy?
But first we have to look somewhere.
Mrs. To.
where is she
Stay here.
I will talk to him myself.
What brings you here today?
You sent me a wedding present
which I did not deserve.
It seemed like you wanted to
preserve the value of shares.
But when it comes to destroying me
you don't care about corporate image.
Nothing will prevent the truth from being revealed.
I didn't know the word "truth"
can be used like this.
The truth is that
what the majority wants to believe.
And you really deserved this gift.
Mrs. Chu once said,
that gave birth to the devil's child.
I think mom is better
knows his child above all others.
She even put you behind bars
to make him come to his senses.
But she did not succeed.
I've always been curious.
You really knocked that person down
by mistake while intoxicated?
Do…
you pressed the gas pedal
on purpose?
Why don't you find out for yourself?
To To Hee!
is everything ok
You should always be careful.
Everyone has bad days.
Like that scoundrel I beat up.
What a coward.
He shot me in the back.
It's always like that in war.
Maybe you married her for show
but had to guard for real.
Come on.
We have to win the war.
See her look?
I have frost outside my skin.
Everything is always visible at first glance.
She proposed to him at the wedding,
where everyone was sad
and immediately got married.
She seemed to be waiting for the death of Chu head.
The government
must punish such maniacs
for the common good and…
What's going on?
I received a lot of donations.
are you having fun
Lord!
You are To To Hee.
You look better in real life.
How much were you paid?
I know who paid you for it.
What are you talking about?
I have no idea.
I was paid in bitcoin.
It looks like that. It is useless to wait for such a mistake.
So who is it? But Suk Min? But Su An?
Hold on. Who else could it be?
What do you wish for?
How suddenly
There must be a reason why you do it.
I just want fame and money.
I can fulfill your wish.
What?
where are we
In a Bank of Korea safe.
What?
Devil!
Unbelievable! How many can there be?
Are you a wizard or something?
Since now you have money
time to get glory.
- How?
- We will leave you here.
When the bank opens in the morning,
you will be caught in the act.
Your photo and name will be in all the news.
- What?
- We'll see you in the news.
Sir, wait!
I will do what you say.
- All that I will say?
- Yes.
- No.
- Please!
You must have recharged well.
The forces have returned.
I know I worried in vain.
what do you want
Where did they hide the instructions for the demons?
You did a great job this time.
I put it on the shelf.
I can't find her.
By the way, the sound quality is excellent.
It's like you're just behind me.
I am behind you.
God!
Lord
I will never get used to it.
Why can't you find the book? Here she is...
She is not here.
Could have sworn he put it there.
I said She is not there.
Are you sure you didn't put it somewhere else?
HISTORY OF "SUNVOL FOUNDATION"
I haven't touched it since we read it together.
And you didn't rummage through my things?
No.
“Jung Il Won, Jung Yi Won, Jung Sam Won…”
That is, one, two and three?
It seems that everyone around me
have a tendency to take other people's things.
And the next name
will be Sip Won, meaning "ten won".
I don't think so.
But it is so.
Pal Won - "eight won",
Ku Won - "nine won".
Sip Won - "ten won".
I will not live with that name.
Why not? I like it.
Easy to pronounce.
Sip Vaughn.
Jung Seop Won.
She is right.
Tradition is the main thing in our foundation.
Support this tradition.
There was no need to start
on behalf of Jung Il Won.
What is the name of the missing book?
I will help you look for her.
The name is simply "Demon".
It is green with something similar
on the eye on the root.
Oh, yes.
He was so protective of her
what I thought was his diary.
What kind of book is this?
This is an instruction to demons.
What is he, an air purifier?
do you see And she thinks…
I will gladly read it when we find it.
Why should you read it?
Because I use a demon as a bodyguard.
"Using"?
And you use me to recharge.
This is true.
So what is written in that book?
Etymology of the word "demon",
forces and their application,
restrictions and...
So
this is an important book.
Limitation? I didn't know you had them.
So…
It's a secret, so I can't tell you.
What's gotten into you, Mr. Puck?
Usually your mouth doesn't close.
I am a professional butler.
RECEPTION
Their powers?
“Demon Limitation.
Demons cannot interfere in God's affairs.
They cannot kill the living
or raise the dead.
They cannot prevent natural disasters...
For violation of this rule
they are destroyed by spontaneous combustion."
Just move us to where the book is.
you can find a person
if you know what she looks like.
You can find a book like this.
It doesn't work with items.
My powers only work on my face.
Your powers are surprisingly limited.
But there is another way.
It is not on the shelves.
Where did you hide it?
Check video cameras.
It was either misplaced or stolen.
Who would steal? No one knows about her.
Choo Seok Hoon wonders who I am.
- Really?
- He asked if I was a vampire.
He bit me.
But this is not the work of his hands.
He would never sneak in
I would not steal anything from anyone.
We don't know that.
Why do you trust him and no one else?
Last rehearsal. Sorry.
Rehearsal?
Reduce the brightness. It's too bright now.
Nice to see your hard work.
I'll show everyone
why am I called Star Chin.
Perfectly.
Are you going to be okay?
Of course.
Their marriage is equally just for show.
It was perfect!
What do you say?
It was wonderful.
The beauty of the performance made it even sadder.
I didn't do it for you.
Why didn't you praise her?
She is finally rehearsing again
and tries so hard.
I saw it in a dream.
Memory from the time when I was human.
What?
The woman in my dream danced like…
"SUNVOL FOUNDATION"
She was amazing.
I used to think she was just an evil woman.
Maybe she's sensitive because she's an actress.
What is it?
What are you talking about?
You seem to be a bit out of your mind
since we watched the show.
empty
Let me take you home.
Do you need somewhere?
There will be a press conference soon.
As an executive director
at least I have to be present.
Again?
Jung Ku Won.
Why now?
What's going on?
What should we do?
Have you not come to your senses yet, you scoundrels?
Run to count "three".
I will beat you to the bone today.
One, two, three.
Boss!
- Boss!
Sit.
Please be our boss, boss!
- What?
- Us, Wild dogs,
someone as powerful as you is needed.
With your…
With your strength
the whole country... No.
The whole world will be ours!
- Really?
- Yes, sir!
Perfectly!
Then…
let's go
- Boss?
- Boss!
Don't follow me or…
Do you know what it can do?
Don't follow me.
Seriously, didn't I tell you
unfollow me?
- They say...
- Don't follow me!
- ...only the brave deserve a good boss.
- Away!
I…
okay?
Boss…
"DEMON"
Because I use a demon as a bodyguard.
"Using"?
And you use me to recharge.
That's true.
So what is written in that book?
Etymology of the word "demon",
forces and their application,
restrictions and...
EXECUTIVE, ABRAXAS
First let's get rid of the obstacle.
Haven't you read the book?
He is not human. He is a monster.
No, he was a man,
until To To Hee appeared.
He can't kill you
and you can kill him.
As soon as you kill him, you will become a devil.
See you later.
when will you come back
I'm just worried
that you will run away from home again.
I won't be long.
I need to recharge as soon as possible.
I want to thank all the reporters
who attended the performance today.
The star of the evening has just returned
from touring Europe.
It's not a circus, it's just that.
The youngest title holder
Intangible cultural heritage
in the Pyongannam-to dance.
Beyoncé of traditional Korean dance!
Chin Ka Yeon!
What brought you, children...
You are under arrest for murder
Chairman Choo Seong-suk.
Give?
You have the right to remain silent
and the right to a lawyer.
everything you say
can be used against you in court.
Ah, it's better to leave it alone.
Just blame fate.
Who blames fate?
You have yourself to blame.
No one will stop the roulette wheel,
if it is already spinning.
All you have to do is make a choice.
Police of Sokho arrested the general director
To To Hee on charges of murder.
General Director To is suspected of murder
the head of "Mire Group" Chu Seong Suk...
It's not over yet, is it?
Actually,
now it's all over.
They can't detain you
without evidence for more than 48 hours.
So hold on a little longer.
Sook Min should know that there is no evidence.
So why does he go so far?
They just need a headline,
that I have been arrested
on a felony charge.
Public criticism
will give them reasons
reject my candidacy.
Don't worry.
Everything will be fine.
Starting the hunt for the monster.
Mrs. Sin
Mrs. To was arrested.
"SUNVOL FOUNDATION"
I'm sorry.
It hurts, right?
To To Hee.
MY BELOVED DEMON
Please let me see you.
He was stabbed!
Too late.
I'm late.
You killed Principal Chong!
All this happened because of you.
What kind of egoist will you be?
It is time to use Director Jeong,
time to let him go.
I want to announce something.
To prevent further
conflicts and disputes,
I withdraw my candidacy.
He may not live to see the morning.
Hold on.
Just a little more.
Translation of subtitles: Daria Hochel